Inventory of the F. Bruce Lamb papers, 1930-1994
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Series III. Publications and Writings, 1939-1994
  - Sub-series 8. Correspondence, 1949-1994
    - Correspondence: Reprints, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence: Hans Peter Duerr about German publication, 1984-1987 (Box 3)
- Series IV. Research Materials, 1938-1992
  Newspaper clippings, articles, reports and printed materials on various topics of forestry, the environment and ecology, science and technology, and the Amazon.
  - Newspaper Clippings, Articles, and Reports on the Environment, the Amazon, Forestry Issues, 1938-1992 (Box 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Articles, and Reports on Forestry, Science, and Enviromental Issues, 1962-1977 (Box 21)